我仍然不知道 世界之大 何处为家
I still don't know where we fit in the world.
我以为放弃信仰就能减轻
I thought leaving faith behind would relieve
我一直以来的负罪感
the dissonance I always felt.
并没有
It didn't.
一路走来 才发现我一直试图抓住某些价值
Through it all, I find myself holding onto these values.
我曾经的属灵同伴 Chris也一样
So does Chris, my former mission companion.
出于某些原因 在探索这条道路上
For one reason or another, we've had trouble
我们遇到了麻烦
finding our way.
我已经一年没有见过他了
It's been a year since I've seen him,
明天他就要回来北镇了
and tomorrow, he comes back to the Northwest.
我们已经说好忘记以前的事重新开始
We've agreed to put it all behind us and start fresh,
不受教会家庭和距离或者其它什么事
uninhibited by the Church, our families, distance,
的影响
or anything else.
这是我们应得的
We deserve that.
所有人都是
Everyone does.
* 你是否想坠落 *
* Don't you wanna fall *
* 你是否想翱翔 *
* Don't you wanna fly *
* 你是否想垂吊悬崖边 *
* Don't you wanna be dangled over the edge *
* 体验危险浪漫 *
* Of this aching romance *
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hey. - Hey.
真不敢相信 你明天就回来了
I cannot believe you're going to be here tomorrow.
我也是
I know.
终于可以把你介绍给我的朋友了
I can introduce you to all my friends finally.
我也可以把你介绍给我朋友
I can introduce you to my friend.
嗨
Hi.
- 嗨 Kaylee  - 海
- Hi, Kaylee.  - Hi.
你好吗
How are you?
很好
Good.
真受不了 你是在太可爱了
You are so cute, I can't even stand it.
已经超过睡觉时间了
It's past her bedtime.
想要道个晚安吗
Do you want to say goodnight?
- 晚安  - 晚安 Kaylee
- Goodnight. - Goodnight, Kaylee.
好了 带上Gillian 去洗漱一下
All right, wanna take Gillian, and go brush all your guys' teeth.
上帝保佑你
God bless you.
祝你健康
Gesundheit.
我马上就要见到你了
I'll be in tuck you in just a sec, okay.
很高兴能见到你
I'm so excited to see you.
我也很高兴能见到你
I know, it'll be good to see you, too.
我想我也该睡了
I better hit the hay as well.
耶 嗯
Yeah, um...
额 既然我们讨论了这事
Uh... so I know that we discussed this,
看得出来你一直想要知道
and I know that you're trying to figure it all out,
我想说的是
but I just want to say that...
我很欢迎她下次
you know, she's more than welcome
能够和你一起来
to come up with you next time you come up,
如果没关系的话
if that's okay.
耶 不是  我会考虑的
Yeah, no, I'll think about that.
很好
Okay, great.
嗯 晚安 再见
Well, goodnight, I'll see you soon.
耶 晚安
Yeah, goodnight.
我爱你 我爱你 Chris
I love you, I love you, Chris.
就是 我爱你
Just... I love you.
我为什么无法像正常人那样说呢
Why can't I just say that like a normal person?
RJ?
Okay 耶 嗨
Okay, yeah, hi.
嗨 不是 我还在 需要我挂电话吗
Hi, no, I'm still here, did you want me to hang up?
- 额 当然 这  - 或者我挂
- Well, sure that'd be... - Or I can.
我不想挂你的电话
Not that I want to hang up on you.
- 我知道  - 好
- No, I know. - Okay.
- 好了 晚安  - 耶 晚安
- Alright, goodnight. - Yep, goodnight.
拜
Bye.
* 骑那大家伙 *
* Ride the big one *
* 你是否想坠落 *
* Don't you wanna fall *
* 你是否想翱翔 *
* Don't you wanna fly *
* 你是否想垂吊悬崖边 *
* Don't you wanna be dangled over the edge *
* 体验危险浪漫 *
* Of this aching romance *
* 我想知晓是否已到尽头 *
* If it's going to end then I wanna know *
* 用尽我的一生 *
* Let me squeeze out every moment *
* 此生若无余剩 *
* But if there's nothing left *
* 可否知晓我缘由 *
* Can you tell me why *
* 你怀抱我时 *
* That it is you're holding onto me *
* 犹如坠入世界的尽头 *
* Like it's the end of the world *
嗨
Hey.
谢谢你来接我
Thanks for coming to get me.
你看起来很帅
You look good.
- 谢谢  - 你是不是瘦了
- Thank you. - I think I lost a little weight.
看起来更帅
It looks good.
谢谢
Thanks.
真高兴你能来
I'm really happy you're here.
从没想过你还愿意和我说话
I didn't think you'd ever speak to me again after the...
我说过原谅你了 我是认真的
I said I forgive you, and I meant it.
我想别人肯定很疑惑
I just think people were legitimately confused
为什么两个男人会在我父母的结婚纪念日上接吻
why two men were kissing at my parents' anniversary party.
我只是在陈述事实
I was trying to make a statement.
嗯 任务完成
Well, mission accomplished.
你知道我很高兴你能见一下Adina和Sheris
You know I'm excited for you to meet Adina and Sheris.
耶 他们听起来很棒
Yeah, they sound great.
还有我的朋友Ryan
Any my friend Ryan.
他是之前回来的教士
Oh he is the returning missionary
你是在跟我讲
you were telling me about?
很好
Great.
是的 我会出席
Yeah, I'll be there.
好的 代我问好
Okay, give her my love, please.
好的 谢谢
Alright, thank you.
好 拜
Okay, bye.
有时候感觉我们好像还没离婚
Sometimes it feels like I'm still married.
谢谢
Thanks.
你饿了吗
You hungry?
我吃得下
I could eat.
我在这会让你们难堪吗
Am I that hard to be around?
不会
No.
医疗销售怎么样
So how is life after pharmaceutical sales?
额 到目前为止还没听到
Well, I haven't heard back from any of the schools
任何回应
that I've applied to.
我对这事倒不担心
I've got my heart set on sticking close to home.
你的写作怎么样了
What about you, how's work?
还不错
Work's going well.
只是有段时间没写了
I haven't written anything original in a while.
我忘了跟你说
I forgot to tell you my sister read
我妹妹看过你的一本书
one of your books.
哦 哪一本
Oh, which one?
暗黑的那本
The really dirty one.
耶 告诉她我很抱歉
Yeah, tell her I'm sorry.
只是她知道你是在说我
It's just that she knew you were talking about me,
就好像
and it was like...
我知道 这就是为什么我要道歉
I know that's why I'm apologizing.
Chelsea最近怎么样
How is Chelsea?
她很好 只是Greg的事我没说
She's good, it's Greg that I don't talk to,
但你已经知道了
but you already knew that.
他们知道你现在在这里吗
Do they know that you're here with me right now?
我妈知道
My Mom does.
至于我爸 他
My Dad, he's...
我们谈谈吧
Let's loosen up.
好的
Okay.
不 我不喝酒
No, I don't drink.
喝吧 你又不去哪里
Come on, you have no where else to be.
我多久才见你一次
How often do I get to see you?
好吧 就一罐
Alright, I'll do one.
再来一罐
Another one?
- 你不该让我喝醉的  - 我才刚到这
- You know you can't get me drunk. - I just got here.
我没有想让你喝醉 自然而然的
I'm not trying to get you drunk, it's just happening.
我们为什么需要这么久才能变得舒适
Why does it take us so long to get comfortable?
我不知道
I don't know.
感觉在你面前 我还是会紧张
I feel like I still get...nervous around you.
耶 我也会紧张
Yeah, I get nervous, too.
虽然已经过了这么久了
After all this time.
耶 因为我们都有一颗火热的心
Yeah, we're just two fluttering hearts.
- 我好想你  - 我也是
- I missed you. - I missed you.
知道吗 我觉得我可以做
You know, I think I can do
任何疯狂的事
this whole Northwest thing.
什么 你做过了
What? You are doing it.
什么
What?
你有和男人约会
You're hanging out with gay, bearded men,
而且你喝酒
and you're drinking beer.
盐湖城怎么样
And what about the Salt Lake City thing?
什么方面的
What about it?
你可以吗
Could you do it?
我觉得你完全可以
I think you could barely do it.
额 也行你最好不要
Well, maybe you won't have to.
好
Okay.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我进去拿点啤酒
I am headed back to your house to get some more beer.
你不是说过不喝的嘛
I thought you said you weren't drinking.
你 帅哥 把门打开
You, sir, have opened the flood gates.
我已经没有退路了
I'm past the point of no return.
你不能就这样放弃
You can't just say that and then walk away.
太迟了
Too late.
拜托
Come on, ugh.
你能行的
You'll be okay.
- 我认为它  - 有点干
- I think it's... - It's a little dry.
我们会没事的
We'll be okay.
我很好
I'm good.
- 嘿 你 额   - 自从上次分开
- Hey did you... - sleep with anybody else
你和其它人上过床吗
since I saw you last?
离开盐湖城后我和Paul做过一次
I had sex with Paul after Salt Lake.
这个我知道
I knew about that.
我说的是之后
I saw you after that.
有 我只是不知道还能再见到你
Yeah, I just didn't know if I'd ever see you again.
别担心
Don't worry about it.
你有男朋友吗
Was there anybody else?
嗯 或者一夜情什么的
Um, like a night here, and a night there, but nothing real.
耶 我有破坏婚姻的坏习惯
Yeah, I had to break a couple bad habits myself.
还有什么比这更坏
What makes them bad?
只是 换个地方
Just, oing places, and...
认识新朋友
meeting people.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think about that?
我觉得我们不应该一直这样
I think that we shouldn't feel like we're bad people
妄自菲薄
all the time.
做爱很正常 你懂的 我们是需要发泄的
It's okay to have sex, you know, we're supposed to cum.
我们本应该如此的
We're supposed to cum.
我们是动物 这很正常
We are animals, it's okay.
我们很正常
We're okay.
不要 不要随意断定我
You're not, you're not going to judge me?
我没有
No.
我只是希望我们能够打开天窗说亮话
I just wanted to get it all out in the open.
耶 这样很好
Yeah, it's fine.
我们把所有的事情摊开讲清楚
We can get everything out in the open.
还有多少件事没有摊开讲
Every last thing we can get out in the open.
三件 两件 一件
Three, two... one.
嘿
Hey.
早上好
Good morning.
喝咖啡吗
Do you want some coffee?
我是摩门教的 先生
I am a Mormon, sir.
你现在是一个摩门教徒
So now you're a Mormon?
阿门
Amen.
起来 起来
Get up, get up.
起来
Get up.
Oh.
什么
What?
我喘口气
My breath.
我不在乎 快点
I don't mind, come on.
我知道
I do.
快点 快
Come on, go.
我还没有准备好
I wasn't ready for that.
那你为什么叫我去做
Then why did you tell me to do it?
开个玩笑
I'm just kidding.
我去买点早餐
I'll go make us some breakfast.
嘿 你想要鸡蛋吗
Hey, how do you want your eggs cooked?
怎么这么亮
Everything's so bright.
因为现在是白天
It's called day.
谢谢你的早餐
Thank you for breakfast.
不用谢
You're welcome.
你头在哪受伤的 那里吗
Where does your head hurt, there?
这里  喔
Right here. Oh.
嗯 你应该多喝点水
Well, you gotta drink more water.
继续
Keep going.
来 我去给你拿点
Here, I'm going to get you some more.
- 谢谢  - 嗯嗯
- Thank you. - Mm-hmm.
"新来的教会指导表示同性家庭的孩子
"New IDS guidelines say children of same-sex couples...
不能接受洗礼仪式"
will not be baptized in the Church."
我知道你想争论这个
I know you want to discuss this,
但是能不能给我点时间
but if you'll just give me a moment
- 读完这篇报道  - 他们开玩笑的 对吗
- to read the whole article. - They're joking, right?
上面说由于同志家庭的小孩不能被同等对待
It says they're doing this for their own protection,
所以这样做是为了
that children from gay marriages can't be treated
保护他们
like everyone else.
免受更多来自同志父母的罪恶
Punishing children for the sins of their own fathers.
真不敢相信
We don't even believe in that.
其实我本可以骗你的
You can interpret this any way you want,
只是我已经说完了
but I am done.
我觉得你不会这么做
I don't think you mean that.
这是Adina
That's Adina.
哈喽 嗨
Hello, hi!
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi!
我是Adina 久仰大名
I'm Adina, I've heard so much about you.
我是Chris
I'm Chris.
耶 我知道
Yeah, I know.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
耶 这是什么
Yeah, what's this?
什么
What?
你的挚爱终于回来了
The love of your life is finally here,
你却给他这个
and you make him this?
额 我只有这个
Well, it's all I had.
Sheris去哪了
Where's Sheris?
不清楚
Not sure.
一切都还好吧
Is everything okay?
不怎么好 不过我没事
No, but I'll be fine.
来吧
Come on.
什么
What?
我又不舌吻 来吧
I'm a lip kisser, come on.
哦
Oh?
什么 你如果和女人结过婚 那就无所谓了
What, you were married to a woman once, you'll be fine.
他的嘴唇好软
He has soft lips.
来回吗?
Back and forth?
是的，你知道这就像…
Yeah, you know it's like...
不，那是上上下下的。
No, that's up and down.
在一起
Together.
我猜人们是上下便便的
I assume that people poop up and down.
好了，继续，有眼睛的习惯。
Okay, moving on, having anuses for eyes.
-嗨。嘿。-嗨。
- Hey. Hey. - Hey.
嘿,女孩。-嗨。
- Hey, girl. - Hi.
-嗨。瑞安。—克里斯。
- Hey. Ryan. - Chris.
哦，很高兴终于见到你了。
Oh, it's great to finally meet you.
—谢谢。-很高兴见到你
- Thank you. - Nice to meet you.
Hey.
Ryan. - Anya.
Steve. Nice to meet you.
-嗨。——嘿,老兄。
- Hey. - Hey, buddy.
哦，你们开始没有我了?
- Oh, you guys started without me?
-是的，我们有一些很棒的，
- Yeah, we had some really great ones,
但是你还是可以自己处理。
but you can still deal yourself in though.
但是你得赶上来
But you gotta catch up.
是的，拿七，挑两个。
Yeah take seven and pick two.
克里斯，你在城里呆多久?
Chris, how long are you in town for?
哦,就在明天
Oh just through tomorrow.
你在工作还是?
You have work or?
我有一个六岁的女儿。
I have a six-year-old daughter.
哦!——真的吗?
- Oh! - Really?
你做什么，瑞恩?
And what do you do Ryan?
哦,我是一个按摩师。
Oh, I'm a masseur.
你这样做多久了?
How long have you been doing that?
哦，我刚刚毕业，所以我才刚刚开始。
Oh, I actually just graduated, so I'm just starting out.
实际上RJ是我唯一的客户。
Actually RJ is my only client.
你是唯一的客户吗?
You're only client?
是的，我希望它能起飞。
Yeah, I'm hoping it'll take off.
这主要是口头上的，但他给了我很多。
It's mostly word of mouth, but he's giving me lots
的练习
of practice.
我们都知道他有多紧张。
We all know how tense he gets, right.
哇，可能是一个网站或名片。
Wow, maybe like a website or business cards.
是的，你知道，我也要处理这方面的事情。
Yeah, you know, I gotta handle that side as well.
我感觉到了
I'm feeling it out, literally.
好卡。-它也很精确
- Good card. - It's so accurate, too.
轮到你。——哦,当然,好的。
- Your turn. - Oh, sure, okay.
一生的礼物，一份悲伤的工作:故事。
Lifetime presents, A Sad Handjob: The Story
一个同性恋排球的蒙太奇。
of a Homoerotic Volleyball Montage.
我的手表。
I'd watch that.
我真不敢相信我和你一起抽大麻，克里斯。
I can't believe I'm smoking pot with you, Chris.
你爸爸是法定人数的一员。
Your dad's a member of the Quorum.
是的,他是Yes he is.
-是啊，这很难。
现在就给我们一个。
- Yeah, that's a tough
one for us right now.
是的,我听到……
-但这是意料之中的事。
- Yeah, I heard...
- but to be expected.
那你上哪儿去了?
你的使命,瑞安?
- So where did you serve
your mission, Ryan?
-我完成了我的使命。
在墨西哥城
- I spent my mission
in Mexico City
这是美丽的…
我的同伴也是如此。
it was beautiful...
and so was my companion.
连续一年……
For a year straight...
他总是改变
在我的面前……
he would always change
in front of me...
完全无辜的,
但他知道自己在做什么。
totally innocent,
but he knew what he was doing.
然后一个晚上,
我们在公共汽车上
And then one night,
we were on a bus
回到我们的地区，然后。
我趴在他的肩膀上睡着了
heading back to our district, and
I fell asleep on his shoulder.
回到我们的地区，然后。
我趴在他的肩膀上睡着了
While I was sleeping,
he had taken my hand,
他拿着它。
在一个男权控制。
and he was holding it
in a patriarchal grip.
我醒来……像这样…I woke up... like this...
我抬头一看
到他的眼睛,……
and I looked up
into his eyes, and...
我看到了欲望和爱。
和渴望……
但我也看到了
这深深的悲伤…
因为我们都知道
我们永远不能在一起……
就在这一刻。
在公共汽车的后面。
我们很快就被送回家了。
从那以后我就没见过他。
但是看到你们
在一起这么长时间后…
它给了我希望。
我要走了。
——真的吗?
-是的…
-很高兴见到你。
——是的,你也一样。
-你还好吗?
——不是。
——嘿,嘿,嘿…
爱你。
——爱你。
你们在哪里认识的?
-嗯，我们是在肯定的时候认识的。
就像一个互助小组。
康复的摩门教徒。
-是的，我知道那是什么。
-是的，他父母踢了。
他离开了房子。
——哇。
——我不知道,
我为他感到难过。
他在这里没有
没有家人或朋友。
——哇。
——你明白吗?
-是的。
——你要来吗?
——哦,对不起。
——没关系。
-你和Ryan有没有…
——没有。
-他肯定爱你。
-你爱我吗?
你想喝点水吗?
那些是什么?
-哦，我有压力。
点在我的后背。
-你的背怎么了?
-只是那些年而已。
拎着一个沉重的手提箱。
——谢谢。
-是的。
-哇，有点冷。
我能问你个问题吗?
——确定。
你会考虑去吗?
和我的圣礼?
-克里斯，我就是不喜欢。
知道要点是什么。
-我觉得不是。
巧合,你住
只有几个街区
远离战争。
现在回来还不晚。
-你以为我去哪儿了?
-不远，除非所有这些。
客厅里的东西。
只是一场表演。
-我还在想办法。
他们努力
我想说的是。
顺便说一下…
你知道吗?
——什么?
-关于政策，做了。
你知道在他们制造之前。
这一消息?
——没有……你真的认为
这一点我知道。
-我不知道，我只是…我不
知道吗，我想如果你做了，
也许有一些
你本可以做的。
——我不知道。
——就像什么?
-跟你父亲谈谈。
——可能
好,会做什么?
-我不知道，他。
像一个内心的声音。
十二门徒之中有一个
使徒们有一个同性恋的儿子。
如果那不是预言，
那我就不知道是什么了。
你想过吗?
会是什么样子呢?
——什么?
-我想起来了。
所有的时间…
和你在一起,结婚……
在教堂
上面的封口机,
我的父母和你的父母。
我做……但它不是
将会发生什么。
不是这样的。
你知道教会做什么吗?
他们更让我信服。
也许是约瑟夫·史密斯。
真的把一切都搞砸了。
——不要这样做。
你怎么能成为其中的一份子呢?
疏远了的东西
父母从孩子吗?
你不理解
这对你意味着什么?
-我一直坚持。
教会的一切。
缺陷和特质,
就像我一直和你在一起一样。
这些年来。
-你在说什么?
我完成了,
我已经填满。
-不，你放弃了，
这是不同的。
-你没有。
离开的勇气。
-我不想离开。
-你好吗?
对待你的方式，
或者他们对待你的方式。
家人和你的女儿吗?
作为一个父亲,如何
你接受吗?
-我所做的一切都是为了她。
你可以质疑我的信仰。
作为一个有信仰的人，
但你从来没有质疑过。
我对我女儿的忠诚。
——我很抱歉。
我很抱歉。
-我在这里做什么?
我在做什么?
我只是觉得有义务
你,你知道的。
我只是不断
回来,回来
因为这是我所知道的一切。
——哇。
——瑞奇?
-嘿…你还好吗?
嘿。
怎么了?
你还好吗?
哇,哇,哇。
简单,简单,
好吧。
怎么了?嘿,看着我……
我就在这里。
呼吸……你还好吗?
-我有时会得到这些。
——嘿,嘿…好了,
好吧。
回到现实生活中。
-这就是现实生活。
对不起,我们继续
他妈的。
-你不必道歉。
——好的。
——谢谢。
——叫克里斯。
——比如列表
一个你…
调用移动
克里斯的数量。
- - - - - -你好。
-克里斯，克里斯，我刚听说。
我很抱歉。
有什么我能帮忙的吗?
你会考虑
来到盐湖城?
是的。
——我可以
所有的安排。
-不，别担心。
——我将到达那里。
-服务是明天。
——是的,那很好。
——好吧,
我会把所有的细节都发给你。
我将很快见到你。
-你还好吗?
——这将是
很高兴你能来。
-是的，我想。
在那里与你在一起时的感觉。
-再见，RJ。
-好吧，我爱你。
——美林的老人
当他看到你的时候，他会大发雷霆。
我想我想
和你在一起。
——嗯…
-我想我应该。
独自做这件事。
——看,儿子,
我从没告诉过你，但是…
我和他谈过了。
等待,什么时候?
-你来的时候我们都在聊天。
在盐湖城和克里斯在一起。
我有点直接。
——怎么这么?
——现在并不重要。
那时我有我的理由。
——嗯…好吧。
妈妈认为什么?
-她支持我。
-你的脚呢?
-没事的，RJ。
——好的。
-好的，儿子，再见。
在盐湖城的早晨。
——是的,我将会看到
你在早上。
——好吧,再见。
——再见。
你今天要去哪里?
——呃,犹他州。
-你会检查吗?
今天包吗?
-不,谢谢。
-好了，先生，
有一个好的飞行。
——谢谢。
——嗨,谢谢。
嘿。
谢谢你的光临。
Hi.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
凯莉- Hi, Kaylee.
- Hi.
你看起来真漂亮。
- You look really pretty.
—谢谢。
-我喜欢你的鞋子。
- Thank you.
- I like your shoes.
-她有点害羞。
- She gets a little shy.
- 没关系
- It's okay.
-我很高兴你在这里
- I'm glad you're here.
- Me too.
绝对是的,你想
和奶奶一起去,亲爱的?
- Hey, shall I take
her for a little why?
绝对是的,你想
和奶奶一起去,亲爱的?
Yeah absolutely, you wanna
go with Grandma, honey?
Yeah.
I'll see you later, sweetie.
你看起来很好
You look good.
- You too.
- Thanks.
我很抱歉。
这是一个非常艰难的局面。
- I'm sorry.
- It's a very tough situation.
这是具有挑战性的,是的。
-是的。
- It's challenging, yeah.
- Yeah.
-你还好吗?
- Are you okay?
-是的，他在这边走。
- Yeah, he's walking over here.
-没事的。
——我在这里
- It's gonna be fine.
- I'm right here.
我觉得他们
开始认识我。
- I think they're
starting to recognize me.
他们可能是。
- They probably are.
嘿，别吻我。
Hey, just don't kiss me.
对不起,这不是有趣的。
Sorry, that wasn't funny.
- RJ.
-梅里尔，我要你。
知道我很抱歉你的损失。
- Elder Merrill, I want you to
know I'm very sorry for your loss.
我很欣赏这一点
- I appreciate that.
克里斯没有告诉我
你要来
Chris didn't tell me
that you were coming.
-我邀请了他，爸爸。
- I invited him, Dad.
—老美林,
我是汤姆·史密斯，RJ的父亲。
- Elder Merrill,
I'm Tom Smith, RJ's father.
哦,是的。
- Oh, right.
-我都不知道。
你现在正在经历。
- I can't begin to know what
you're going through right now.
说对不起是不够的
来表达我的同情。
Saying sorry isn't enough
to express my sympathies.
-谢谢你，史密斯兄弟。
- Thank you, Brother Smith.
你一定是克里斯，史密斯兄弟。
——是的。
- And you must be Chris, brother Smith.
- Yes.
我听说很多
对你的伟大的事情。
I've heard so many
great things about you.
Welcome.
What happened?
-哦，工作上出了事故。
- Oh, an accident at work.
老史密斯,
我以为是你。
- Elder Smith,
I thought that was you.
How are you?
- RJ, are you okay, son?
- I'm sorry.
- RJ?
抱歉
- Excuse me.
容易,嘿,容易。
Easy, hey, easy.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
-太奇怪了。
-是的。
- That was so weird.
- Yeah.
-我们的使命总统…
- Our mission president...
还有你父亲的长相。
给了我，他恨我。
and the look that your father
gave me, he hates me.
—好的。好吧。
-他不恨你。
- Okay. Okay.
- He doesn't hate you.
-我只是想。
为你在这里。
- I just wanted to
be here for you.
你是，你在这里。
- You are, you're here.
休息。
Rest.
简单,简单,容易
Easy, easy, easy.
好了,
我们走，我们走。
There we go, there
we go, there we go.
-他们会没事的。
- They're gonna be alright.
-是啊，你为什么不呢?
RJ留下来,
- Yeah, why don't you
and RJ stick around,
我们去吃晚餐?
and we'll get some dinner?
-哦，老美林，我做不到。
侵犯你的哀悼。
- Oh, Elder Merrill, I couldn't
intrude on your mourning.
-我们需要谈一谈。
- We need to have a talk.
我们需要一个坦诚的谈话,
We need to have a
candid conversation,
我希望你和RJ。
and I would like you and RJ
今晚和我们一起吃饭，
对吧?
to join us for dinner tonight,
alright?
当然。
- Absolutely.
- Good, thank you.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
所以,我听你的
去了法学院。
So, I hear you're
going to law school.
—我还应用。
- I'm still applying.
-我敢说你妈妈很骄傲。
- I bet your mother was proud.
—是的,她是。
- Yeah, she was.
就她而言，
我已经在练习律法了。
As far as she was concerned,
I was already practicing law.
-我的老任务伙伴。
成为一名律师。
- My old mission companion
became an attorney.
我看见他和我的一些人。
最近其他同伴
I saw him and some of my
other companions recently.
我们相遇了一个晚上。
生活没有跳过节拍，
We met up for a night, and
life didn't skip a beat,
let me tell you.
我们捡起
我们离开的地方。
We picked up right
where we left off.
我们分享我们的祝福,
我们的悲剧,
We shared our blessings,
and our tragedies,
爱和心碎。
love and heartbreak.
他们中的一些人……我不知道
他们正在经历的一切!
Some of them... I had no idea
what they were going through
然后回来。
back then.
很高兴
人们在你的生活中
It's nice to have
people in your life
你可以依赖。
you can depend on.
-我是格雷格，克里斯的弟弟。
- I'm Greg, Chris's brother.
—托马斯·史密斯，RJ的父亲。
- Thomas Smith, RJ's father.
-很高兴再次见到你。
- It's good to see you again.
- Thank you.
你认识我妈妈吗?
Did you know my mother?
-好的，格雷格，我知道。
你不太在乎我，
- Okay, Greg, I know that
you don't care much for me,
所以也许我们应该…
so maybe we should...
-我想坐。
在这里哀悼我的母亲。
- I would like to sit
here and mourn my mother
没有影子
我哥哥过去
without the shadow
of my brother's past
在这神圣的时刻。
looming over this sacred moment.
——我很抱歉。
-可以给我吗?
- I'm sorry.
- May I have that?
-你真的要去。
现在就做，格雷格?
- You're really going to
do this right now, Greg?
-我们爸爸让我去的。
在这里，我在这里。
- Our father asked me to
be here, and here I am.
Dad.
-孩子们，史密斯兄弟，RJ。
- Boys, Brother Smith, RJ.
—老美林。
- Elder Merrill.
- Good to see you.
-我不知道该拿什么，所以我。
吃了各种各样的食物，泰国菜。
- I didn't know what to get, so I
got a variety of foods, pad Thai.
-我希望饭
对每个人都好。
- I hope Thai is
good for everyone.
我们没剩多少了。
招待会后,所以…
We didn't have much left
after the reception, so...
看起来不错，又好又热。
Looks good, nice and hot.
史密斯兄弟,
你喜欢为我们祈祷吗?
Brother Smith, would
you like to pray for us?
—我的美林
如果是会员，就应该受到尊敬。
- Elder Merrill, I'd
be honored if a member
法定人数的
说祝福。
of the Quorum would
say a blessing.
-好吧，叫我诺亚好吗?
- Okay, call me Noah, alright?
—让我们祈祷
- Let's pray.
我们的天父,
谢谢你带来的一切
Our Heavenly Father,
thank you for bringing
汤姆和RJ安全地到我们这里。
今天和我们的家庭。
Tom and RJ safely to us
today and as our families
聚在一起,请帮助
我们引导我们的谈话,
come together, please help
us guide our conversation,
帮助我们了解
对每个人来说都是最好的,
help us discover what
is best for everyone,
以
耶稣基督名义,阿门。
in the name of
Jesus Christ, Amen.
- Amen.
-史密斯兄弟和RJ，
谢谢你们俩
- Brother Smith and RJ,
thank you both
今天在这里，就是这样。
你能来真是太好了。
for being here today, it was
very gracious of you to come.
我必须说清楚。
现在和贝尔的证词
I have to make clear right
now and bear testimony
对你们每个人……
to each of you that...
性的关系
sexual relations
同性是错误的
between two of the
same sex is wrong.
通过这样做，我们的孩子。
成为变节者,
By doing so, our children
become apostates,
并且应该扑杀
的王国
and should be culled
from the kingdom.
现在世界上的其他国家可能会。
走一条不同的路，
Now the rest of the world may
be taking a different path,
但是我们保持忠诚
福音。
but we remain faithful
to the Gospel.
-你做得很漂亮。
大胆的假设,爸爸。
- You've made some pretty
bold assumptions, Dad.
-我见过。
我自己的眼睛,克里斯。
- I've seen it with
my own eyes, Chris.
我读过他的书。
I've read his book.
—有一本书吗?
- There's a book?
-这是一个详细的描述。
他们的使命。
- It's a detailed account
of their mission together.
而你，你感觉如何。
关于这个
And you, how do you feel
about this, having your
每个人看法不一样?
adventures out there in
print for everyone to see?
-我不想让他们指出来。
- I wouldn't want them in print.
-好吧，没人会读。
一本关于你的书，格雷格。
- Well, no one would read
a book about you, Greg.
-你读了整件事吗?
- Did you read the whole thing?
-我尽可能多地读。
- I read as much as I could.
-那部分呢?
他们帮助经验丰富的
- What about the part when
they helped the veteran
创伤后应激障碍使他平静下来。
天上的父亲和他自己。
with PTSD make his peace with
heavenly Father and himself.
你读了吗?
Did you read that?
-你的儿子和我相爱了。
- Your son and I fell in love.
我们做了人们做的事情。
当他们相爱的时候。
We did things that people do
when they love each other.
-信仰不是金赛的尺度。
- Faith isn't a Kinsey scale.
你不是一个有信仰的人，
或者你不是。
You're either a man of faith,
or you're not.
美林，我可以向你保证，RJ…
爸爸。
- Elder Merrill, I can assure you, RJ...
- Dad.
不管你喜欢与否,
我在你的生活。
Like it or not,
I'm in your life.
不管上帝与否，我都能感觉到。
今晚失去了这个女人，
A man of God or not, I feel the
loss of this woman tonight,
我通过他感觉到了。
and I feel it through him.
他是我爱的人。
我爱他的家人。
And he's a man that I love
and whose family I love.
-我妈妈会爱你的。
- My mother would've loved you.
就像我做的事。
Just like I do.
—所以这是什么
要看起来像什么?
- So what's this
going to look like?
—是什么
要看起来像什么?
- What's what
going to look like?
—这一点。- This.
—什么?- What?
你们俩，和他在西雅图?
You two, with him in Seattle?
—好吧,RJ搬到波特兰,爸爸。
- Well, RJ moved
to Portland, Dad.
-这是一样的。
- Well, that's the same thing.
凯莉在盐湖城。
Kaylee's in Salt Lake City.
- RJ和我不是。
现在在一起。
- RJ and I aren't
together right now.
-等一下，我想。
你们是…
- Wait a minute, I thought
that you guys were...
ya know.
—是的,为什么不呢?我刚听到
你说你爱他。
- Yeah why not? I just heard
you say that you love him.
你介意我问一下吗?
问题是什么?
Do you mind if I ask
what the problem is?
-教会…在哪里
我们完全融入其中。
- The Church... and where
we fit inside of it all.
我们不知道。
We don't know.
我明白了
- I see.
Thanks.
RJ,谢谢你
克里斯在这里。
RJ, thank you for
being here for Chris.
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you for coming.
-儿子，帮帮我。 —谢谢
- Son, give me a hand.
- Thanks.
你知道，RJ，我明白了…
克里斯。我的意思。
You know, RJ, I get it...
about Chris. I mean.
我和你妈
想要对你最好的，并且…
Your mother and I
want the best for you, and...
我想不出谁来。
你比他强。
I can't think of anyone
better for you than him.
我想让你知道……
我为你骄傲，儿子。
I want you to know...
I'm proud of you, son.
—为了什么?
- For what?
-……
-做一个好人…
- For...
- being a good human being...
还有坚韧不拔的精神。
……跟随你的心。
and for having the fortitude
to... follow your heart.
我知道有人在
你的情况。
I knew someone in
your situation once.
他不是那样
像你和克里斯一样勇敢。
He wasn't nearly as
courageous as you and Chris.
-是的，我想我记得。
你谈论他。
- Yeah, I think I remember
you talking about him.
你知道
发生在他身上?
Do you know what
happened to him?
他是好的吗?
Is he okay?
- He is... he's fine.
-如果你有的话。
想谈谈他，
- Well if you ever
want to talk about him,
I'll listen.
- Thank you, son.
*看太阳*。
* Looking at the sun *
*你认为只有这样。
天空中的一盏灯*。
* You think there's only
one light in the sky *
*你不会是对的*
* You wouldn't be right *
*等到夜晚来临*
* Wait until the night comes *
看到一万亿的太阳。
旋转上面*
* See a trillion suns
spinning up above *
这就是它的本质。
* That's how it is *
就是这样。
* That's how it is when *
请坐
- Have a seat.
- Is Sheris here?
—她睡着了。
- She's asleep.
—一切都好吗?
- Is everything okay?
是的,我们很好
- Yeah, we're fine.
现在告诉我关于盐湖的事。
Now tell me about Salt Lake.
-是真的。
难过,很甜。
- Well, it was really
sad and really sweet.
我们说再见,
和…现在我在这里。
And we said goodbye,
and... now I'm here.
—不
任何意义。
- Well that doesn't
make any sense.
你们一直在做这个。
六,七年。
You guys have been at this
what, six, seven years.
我爱你，不，
我是摩门教徒，不，我不是。
I love you, no I don't,
I'm Mormon, no I'm not.
我父母会生气的如果我们操，我们不该操
My parents will be mad if
we fuck, we shouldn't fuck.
他妈反对我们的宗教。
Fucking is against our religion.
如果每个人都只会
别再胡闹了。
If everyone would just
stop giving a fuck about
其他人是谁
他妈的就不会
who everyone else was
fucking then there wouldn't
是一个问题。
be a problem.
我不在乎谁。
除了莎丽。
I don't care who anyone
fucks except for Sharis.
我为什么要在乎?
那个家伙诅咒
Why should I care about
who that guy fucks,
或者那个混蛋，或者那个。
盖伊·福克斯，或者那个混蛋，
or that guy fucks, or that
guy fucks, or that guy fucks,
都是废话。
it's all bullshit.
- Yeah, I agree.
-好，那又怎样。
你害怕什么?
- Good, so then what
are you afraid of?
没什么
- Nothing.
-你知道有。
社区的人。
- You know there's a
community of people out there
谁爱你,
希望你快乐。
who love you and
want you to be happy
我们希望你找到真爱。
and we want you to find love.
-你知道，我能做到。
- You know, I could do it.
我可以妥协，如果。
这意味着和他一起生活。
I could-I could compromise if
it meant living a life with him.
-那你为什么不呢?
- So then why don't you?
-因为你不是同性恋，
或者你是个有信仰的人……
- Because you're either gay,
or you're a man of faith...
但显然
你不能两者兼而有之。
but apparently
you can't be both.
- Hey.
- Hi.
-你知道，你知道的停止说话。
- You know, you can tell
her to stop talking.
这就是我做的
That's what I do.
醒着的我。
Waking me up.
Hi.
我听说了克里斯的妈妈。
I heard about Chris's mom.
你过得如何?
How are you doing?
- Eh...
—来到这里。
- Come here.
-你让我感觉像。
当你这样做的时候。
- You make me feel like
a baby when you do that.
-因为你是一个。
- Because you are one.
—不,不,不。
-跟我多做一个。
- No, no, no.
- Do one more with me.
—不,我很好。
-再来一个，来吧。
- No, I'm good.
- Just one more, come on.
-不，真的，我很好。
——好。
- No, really, I'm good.
- Fine.
-你要崩溃了。
- You are falling apart.
我是- - - ?我想我
终于放松了。
- Am I? I think I'm
finally letting loose.
—好吧,你已经
放松一段时间。
- Well, you've been
letting loose for a while.
你需要放松一下。
- Well, you need to loosen up.
我们现在该怎么办?
What do we do now?
-我晕过去了，因为我有。
早上去做编辑。
- Well I pass out because I have
to go be an editor in the morning.
-不，不，不，我是说。
你的身体工作。
- No, no, no, I mean
your body of work.
书架上的那些书，它们是。
充满了你的感情
Those books on the shelf, they're
filled with your feelings
关于这个的人
about this man.
他是你的缪斯女神。
He was your muse.
-我会找到新的。
- I'll find a new one.
-我可以做你的缪斯女神。
- I could be your muse.
I make a great muse.
- Yeah, you are.
- What?
没什么
- Nothing.
- Okay, okay,
no, okay, okay, okay.
—他不在这里。
- He's not here.
-这不关他的事。
- It's not about him.
你被我吸引对吧?
- You're attracted to me right?
- Of course, you're beautiful.
Hey come on, please don't be...
别让这
是我们之间的尴尬。
Don't let this
be awkward between us.
—太迟了。
- Too late.
-听着，我对你有感觉。
- Look, I have feelings for you.
他们是
复杂的感情。
And they are
complicated feelings.
我们就是不能做爱。
We just can't have sex.
它会搞砸了。
It'll mess it up.
-我们都知道那是什么。
爱的东西
- We both know what it's
like to love something
这并不爱
我们回来了,不是吗?
that doesn't love
us back, don't we?
-瑞安…来吧。
- Ryan... come on.
—什么?
- What?
-过来，过来。
- Come here, come on.
Come here.
—你还
相信上帝,RJ吗?
- Do you still
believe in God, RJ?
你认为
他现在在这里吗?
Do you think that
He's here right now?
因为我开始
看到我们的天父…
Because I'm starting to
see our Heavenly Father...
就像我看到了先知。
或者其他领导人，就像…
like I see the Prophet
or the other leaders, as...
有缺陷的人。
flawed men.
我不想
看到这样的他。
I don't want to
see Him like that.
我想知道他是谁。
在这里，他爱我。
I want to know that He's
here, and that He loves me.
-你现在感觉到被爱了吗?
- Do you feel loved right now?
-在这一刻，我愿意。
- In this moment, I do.
-也许他是
- Then maybe He is.
-我不得不承认…
- I have to admit...
我不想要你和克里斯。
工作了。
I didn't want you and Chris
to work out.
—我知道。
- I know that.
-我只是不想。
失去我们拥有的。
- I just didn't want
to lose what we have.
-我不是你想要的，
我想你们都知道。
- I am not what you want,
and I think you know that.
-我看着你们，
我心想，
- I looked at you guys,
and I thought to myself,
“我想要……我想要的。
"I want that... I want that.
或类似的东西。
Or something like that."
-你可以拥有它
- You can have it.
-我想找个家，RJ。
- I want a family some day, RJ.
我想要一个礼堂婚礼
I want a Temple wedding.
我不希望别人告诉我。
我要被驱逐了。
I don't want to be told that
I'm going to be banished
这些希望在外面看来太黑暗。
to the outer darkness
for wanting that.
我去过黑暗的地方，
I have been to the dark places,
and I had to pull myself out.
我不想回去。
I don't want to go back there.
-你可以拥有所有这些，
但如果你走了，就不是了。
- You can have all of that,
but not if you're gone.
-我们现在做什么?
- What do we do now?
我们打电话给你
任务的同伴。
- We call your
mission companion.
-不，不，我们没有。
-是的。是的。
- No, no we don't.
- Yeah. Yeah.
-来吧，有办法吗?
找个老彼得森?
- Come on is there a way to
get a hold of Elder Petersen?
- Maybe.
- Then let's call him.
-可能不是。
他的电话号码。
- It's probably not even
his number any more.
除了他不会
接,他可能
Besides he wouldn't
pick up, he's probably
和他的朋友们
什么的。
out with his friends
or something.
在BYU，就像凌晨2点。
At BYU, it's like 2 am.
-好吧，也许不是，但是。
但他还是不接电话
- Okay, well maybe not, but
still he wouldn't pick up.
- Well then it doesn't matter.
他可能会生我的气。
- He might be angry with me.
- Why?
他回家做我们做的事
- He went home for what we did.
他感到羞愧。
He's ashamed.
-他可能会掉进去。
爱着另一个男孩,
- He could fall in
love with another boy,
更糟的是，他可以结婚。
一些毫无戒心的女孩
or worse, he could marry
some unsuspecting girl.
—我一直在喝酒。
- I've been drinking.
—这只会帮助。
- That'll only help.
-我改天再打给他。
- I'll call him some other time.
-不，不，今晚，我们。
今晚会打电话给他。
- No, no, tonight, we're
gonna call him tonight.
克里斯从来不回答你的问题。
你的使命后调用。
- Chris never answered your
calls after your mission.
-是的，我不够努力。
-好吧，他不让你这么做。
- Yeah, I didn't try hard enough.
- Well, he didn't let you.
-我本可以更努力的。
-别像我那样搞砸了。
- I could've tried harder.
- Don't fuck this up like I did.
—你没有。
- You didn't.
来吧，让我看看你的手机。
- Come on let me see your phone.
—这可能是死了
- It's probably dead.
—你不会
来吧，来吧。
- You're not going
to do it, come on.
-让我来整理一下。
- Just let me sort it out.
—他的室友
可能现在
- His roommates are
probably out right now
与他们的女朋友沉溺。
soaking with their girlfriends.
恶心
- Gross.
-他一个人在宿舍，
他要你给他打电话。
- He's alone in his dorm,
and he wants you to call him.
不,他没有。
- No, he doesn't.
你知道你什么时候想。
你爱的人,
- You know when you think
about someone you love,
通常因为他们
我也想着你。
it's usually because they're
thinking about you, too.
- Hello?
- It's Ryan.
我在波特兰。
I'm in Portland.
That's cool.
你怎么知道我会起床?
How did you know I'd be up?
-只是运气好，我想。
- Just luck, I guess.
很高兴收到你的来信。
It's nice to hear from you.
-太好了。
听到你的声音。
- It's so good to
hear your voice.
很奇怪你会叫,
It's weird you'd called,
我一直在想你。
I've been thinking about you.
—你有吗?
- You have?
—是的,
像所有的翻转时间一样。
- Yeah,
like all the flipping time.
你独自一人吗?
- Are you alone?
Yeah, are you?
- Yeah, I am.
你最近怎么样?
So, how have you been?
- Good.
I miss you.
- I miss you, too.
- Really?
- Yeah.
我真希望能看到你的脸。
- I wish I could see your face.
-也许我们可以。
实现它。
- Well maybe we could
make that happen.
- Really?
- Yeah.
我记得你是如何
过去常常看着我。
- I remember how you
used to look at me.
-就像你是唯一的。
世界上的人吗?
- Like you were the only
person in the world?
- Yeah.
-因为我只看到了这些。
- It's because that's all I saw.
I love you.
- I love you, too.
So much.
我回家,
我认为这是时间
- I'm coming home,
I think it's time.
-主席，我可以坐下吗?
- President, may I sit?
—是的,哥哥美林。
- Yes, brother Merrill.
我先说一下。
我为你祈祷。
Let me first say that
I am praying for you.
我一直在说话
我们的天父,
I've been speaking with
our Heavenly Father,
和他爱你。
and He loves you.
黛比是亲爱的
我和弗朗西斯
Debbie was dear to
me and to Francis.
切尔西和格雷格，
克里斯和凯莉吗?
How are Chelsea, and Greg,
Chris and Kaylee?
-切尔西正在接受。
这很困难，格雷格也是。
- Well Chelsea is taking
it pretty hard, as is Greg.
凯莉,我们告诉她
那个Deedee已经走了
Kaylee, we tell her
that Deedee has gone on
给她永恒的家庭，但是。
你知道，她是个孩子。
to her eternal family, but
you know, she's a child.
克里斯是一个顽固的人
Chris has been a rock.
他实际上是一个
很大一部分原因
And he's actually a
big part of the reason
我今天在这里。
I'm here today.
- Oh?
-他受同性恋的影响很多年
- He suffered from same-sex
attraction for many years.
我尽力了，我什么都做了。
我可以帮助他
I tried, I did everything
I could to help him,
但我现在已经停止了。
but I've stopped that now.
-这是非常困难的。
的情况
- It's a very difficult
situation.
-我意识到他。
他的样子很好。
- I realized that he
is fine the way he is.
没有必要
为他改变。
There's no need
for him to change.
- Brother Merrill,
你知道路西法会的。
试着每一个技巧来误导我们。
you know that Lucifer will
try every trick to mislead us.
,你继续
教我保持开放。
- You continue to
teach me to be open
来促进。
精神，我感觉到我的心。
to the promptings of the
spirit, and I feel my heart
软化对克里斯
和许多忠实的
softening towards Chris
and the many faithful
像他这样的人。
who are like him.
我们的灵性在哪儿?
Where's our spirituality?
我们的反应
给上帝的爱?
Where's our response
to the love of God?
这并不觉得
爱,让人们选择……
This doesn't feel like
love, making people choose...
将自己
从他们的永恒。
separating ourselves
from them for eternity.
你看见什么了吗
世界上发生?
Have you seen what's
happening in the world?
人被杀,
殴打,歧视
People are being killed,
beaten, discriminated against
每一天，我的儿子都在其中。
every day, my son among them.
- I understand,
brother Merrill,但我
从上帝那里得到消息……
brother Merrill, but I
have heard from the Lord...
我们必须继续吗?
我们已经有了。
is that we have to proceed
as we already have.
-我也谈过了。
我们的天父。
- Well, I, too, have talked
to our Heavenly Father.
哦,你有吗?
Oh, have you?
是的，他告诉我了。
我们,使徒,和…
Yes and He told me that
we, the apostles, and...
Quorum必须继续
讨论这件事。
the Quorum must continue
to discuss this matter.
——好了,儿子,你一会还有
你的会议。
- Alright, son, you'll
have your meeting.
与此同时,
诺亚,得到一些休息
In the meantime,
Noah, get some rest.
你正在经历
更多的现在
You're going through
much more now
比你意识到的。
than you may realize.
-谢谢，但我真的。
现在就需要工作。
- Thank you, but I really
need to work right now.
- I understand.
Let us pray.
- Of course.
亲爱的天父,
我们感谢你们的友谊。
- Dear Heavenly Father,
we thank you for the friendships
在困难时期支持我们……
当我们失去家庭
that support us in difficult times...
when we lose family
直到我们看到他们
在永生,
until we see them
again in eternal life,
它是非常困难的。
it is very hard.
—好的。你还记得这
这些在订单吗?
- Okay. Do you remember which
order these go in?
- Yeah.
—好了,把他们
为了我。
- Alright, put 'em
in order for me.
很好,不错。
Very good, good job.
你能告诉我在哪儿吗?
奶奶，你还记得吗?
So can you tell me where
Grandma is, do you remember?
很好，这就是精神世界。
这是天堂。
Very good, that's the spirit world.
That's paradise.
这就是她的
等待我们所有人。
That's where she's
waiting for all of us.
—在这里吗?
——是的,在这里
- Here?
- Yep, right there.
——是的,在这里,
总有一天，我们都会
- Yeah, right there,
and one day, we will all
在一起在这里。
be together right here.
那就是你，我，还有。
妈妈会在那里
So it'll be you, and me, and
Mommy's going to be there,
还有你的奶奶，还有我们。
将永远在一起。
and your Grandma, and we
will all be together forever.
- RJ, too?
是的,当然,
他会在那里
- Yeah, of course,
he'll be there.
当然，他会在那儿的，宝贝。
Of course, he'll be there, baby.
哦，你妈妈要去。
几分钟后到这里。
Oh, your Mommy's going to
be here in a few minutes.
你想去吗?
在外面等她?
Do you want to go
outside and wait for her?
看看我们能不能看到她开车?
See if we can see her drive up?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
-你保证你没疯。
我不会去拜你?
- You promise you're not mad
that I'm not going to BYU?
我不是疯了
- I'm not mad.
这更有意义
This makes so more sense.
你不需要
扰乱Kaylee的生活。
You won't have to
disrupt Kaylee's life.
这个地方很漂亮。
This place is beautiful.
-是的。
- Yeah.
这是正确的事情。
It's the right thing.
我在想我们的事。
与史密斯夫妇共进晚餐,
I was thinking about our
dinner with the Smiths,
我多么希望你这样。
妈妈本来可以去的。
and how much I wished your
mom could have been there
为了那
for that.
它有一个生命标记。
对它的感觉。
It had a life marker
feel about it.
它启发了我
带来一些问题
It's inspired me to
bring some matters up
在法定人数。
before the Quorum.
我要拉一下。
新政策的主题。
I'm going to broach the
subject of the new policy
和同性
在教堂里结婚。
and also same-sex
marriage in the Church.
你怎么看?
What do you think about that?
-我想我没说过。
你,但是……当我在
- I don't think I ever told
you this, but... while I was
在治疗……他们告诉
我一次又一次,
in therapy... they told
me time and again,
你可以选择上帝或。
你可以选择爱。
you can choose God or
you can choose love.
嗯,对我来说,他们是
一个相同的。
Well, to me, they're
one in the same.
我的女儿知道
这是一个孩子知道的。
My own daughter knows
that, a child knows that.
我不会让。
谁能告诉我我能做什么。
I'm not going to let
anyone tell me who I can
不能与…我
不会让任何人……
and can't be with... and I'm
not going to let anyone...
定义这些选择
对我来说。
define those choices
for me either.
这次会议的
总统的群体……
This meeting with the
President, with the Quorum...
谢谢，但我希望你能。
不是为我做的。
thank you, but I hope you're
not doing it just for me.
我希望你正在做的事情
因为你知道
I hope you're doing
it because you know
这是正确的做法。
it's the right thing to do.
作为一名成员。
法定人数,我是有限的
- As a member of the
Quorum, I'm limited.
我只是其中一个声音，但我要去
I'm one voice in that
room, but I'm going to have
你妈妈和我在一起。
your mom with me.
你知道的…当我看到
RJ和你在一起,
You know... when I saw
you and RJ together,
当他惊恐发作时，
你追着他跑…
when he had his panic attack,
and you ran after him...
安慰他,说
他通过它。
reassured him, talked
him through it.
这提醒我
你妈妈和我，
That reminded me so
much of your mom and I,
以及我们是如何互相关心的。
and how we cared for each other.
这是爱。
That's love.
我看到了
I saw that with you.
这就像一个梦想……
It's like a dream...
这种生活,
它只会持续很长时间
this life,
it only lasts so long.
我爱你,儿子。
I love you, son.
- I love you, too, Dad.
-天啊，我真想她。
- God, I miss her.
- Me too.
* His love shall light my way *
* Through darkness
and through doubt *
* Imprisoned by uncertainty *
* His love has brought me out *
- Hey.
- Hi.
你在这里多久了?
- How long have you been here?
-三个半小时。
- Three and a half hours.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
-你进了法学院。
- You got into law school.
—我所做的。
- I did.
—恭喜你。
-谢谢你…哦,好的。
- Congratulations.
- Thank you... Oh, okay.
-你有时间…想吗?
- Have you had time... to think?
你不需要
为我坚强
You don't have to
be strong for me.
-我没必要说再见。
- I never got to say goodbye.
她是如此好。
She was so good.
——嗨,你已经到了
Christopher Merrill的语音信箱。
- Hi, you've reached
the voice-mail box of Christopher Merrill.
-克里斯，作为一个成员。
十二的法定人数，
- Chris, as a member of
the Quorum of the Twelve,
我得告诉你。
我不能支持你,
I have to tell you that
I cannot support you,
但是作为你的父亲,
你有我的祝福。
but as your father,
you have my blessing.
你不需要它,
但是你拥有它。
You don't need it,
but you have it.
-嘿，嘿，你有时间。
- Hey, hey, you have time.
你不会
想念你的航班。
You're not going to
miss your flight.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
会是什么样子呢!
当你开始上学了吗?
What's in going to be like
when you start school?
-你知道的。
现在每个人都要休息。
- Well, you know there's
going to be breaks every now
然后,它
只有三年。
and then, and it's
only three years.
-很多事情都有可能发生。
在三年。
- A lot can happen
in three years.
- Yeah.
-我只是觉得。
你要离开,
- I just feel like
you're going to leave,
和所有的
还是一样的。
and everything's
going to be the same.
- RJ，我知道为什么。
你有这样的感觉
- RJ, I know why
you feel that way.
我今早祈祷了。
- I prayed this morning.
我祈求天上的
父亲给了我力量
I prayed for Heavenly
Father to give me strength.
我祈求力量
让我们去,
I prayed for strength
to let us go,
这样你就可以参加了。
在你自己的生活中
so that you could attend to
matters in your own life,
我也可以这么做
and I could do the same.
我知道教堂
背叛了我们…
I know that the Church
has betrayed us...
它把我们排除在外。
这是……心碎……
and it's excluded us, and
it's been... heart breaking...
但当你
结束了
but when you're
wrapped up in it,
没有它我就活不下去。
I can't live without it.
-我知道这是真的。
疯狂的过去几
- I know it's been really
crazy the last couple
几个星期，对我来说，
我很抱歉……
of weeks, and for my part,
I apologize for that...
但如果它教会了我什么，
but if it's taught me anything,
人生苦短。
it's that life is way too short.
这是我第一次。
生活，我知道我想要什么
For the first time in my
life, I know what I want
和我想要的。
and who I want.
我想要你。
I want you.
还有Kaylee和教堂，
我希望这一切……
And Kaylee, and the Church,
I want it all...
因为我们应得的。
because we deserve it.
-我也想要。
- I want it all, too.
我想要的一切。
I want everything.
它和我们一样属于我们。
它属于任何人……
It belongs to us as much as
it belongs to anyone else...
没人能告诉我们。
我们的选择是……
and nobody can tell us
what our options are...
我也不想
and I don't want to
fuck around anymore.
-嗯，我有一个完整的。
另一件事。
- Well, I had this whole
other thing planned.
我最近打电话给你爸爸…
I called your dad recently...
我打电话给他的原因是。
请求他允许和他儿子结婚。
and the reason I called him was to
ask his permission to marry his son.
你愿意嫁给我吗?
Will you marry me?
Yes...
I love you.
- I love you so much.
我再也不会离开你了。
I will never leave you again.
你需要一些纸巾？
You need some tissue?
- No, no I'm okay.
我要赶飞机。
- I have a plane to catch.
-你说过你不会离开的。
就这一次。
- You said you would never leave.
- Just this once.
- Okay.
-我们亲爱的天父，
我们非常感激
- Our dear Heavenly Father,
we're so very grateful
在这幸福的日子里。
在这里，和这两个年轻人。
for this blessed day, to be
here, with these two young men.
我们祈祷你
灵魂将与我们同在，
We pray that thy
spirit will be with us,
它会保佑他们的和强固他们
and it will bless them
and strengthen them
一起挑战。
as they endure life's
challenges together.
我们祈祷一切都会好起来。
丰富的经验
We pray that all will be
enriched by this experience
我们今天离开,
as we leave today,
我们将永远。
记得对待你的孩子。
and that we will always
remember to treat thy children
爱的极致，
善良,耐心,
with the utmost of love,
kindness, and patience,
我们问这些问题。
以你儿子的名义谦恭地
and we ask these things
humbly in the name of thy Son,
耶稣基督,阿门。
Jesus Christ, Amen.
- Amen.
-现在可以戴戒指戒指。
- And now the rings.
,你们接受
另一个在手上。
Brethren, do you take
one another by the hand
彼此接受。
做你的合法的和结婚的。
and receive each other to
be your lawful and wedded
丈夫时间
和所有的永恒
husband for time
and all eternity,
这是在。
上帝,天使,
and this you do in the
presence of God, angels,
还有你的这些见证人。
自由意志和选择?
and these witnesses of your
own free will and choice?
- Yes.
-被赋予我的权力，
我现在宣布你们为丈夫。
- By the power vested in me,
I now pronounce you husbands.
-我叫RJ Smith，我愿意
嫁给克里斯，我一生的挚爱……
- My name is RJ Smith, and I
married Chris, the love of my life...
2016年12月,
俄勒冈州波特兰市
in December of 2016,
in Portland, Oregon,
我们的家人都在那里，
our families were both there,
包括我的继女Kaylee.
including my stepdaughter
Kaylee.
我很快就到
盐湖。
I soon moved to
Salt Lake with them.
我找到了一份工作。
兼职教授
I got a job as an
adjunct professor
at the University of Utah,
and I finished my new book.
在犹他大学，
我完成了我的新书。
I finally found a way to join the
two opposing sides of myself.
我终于找到了一种加入的方法。
我的两个对立面。
My first day in our home,
we knelt down and prayed.
克里斯轻声对我说，
“就是这样。
Chris said to me softly,
"This is it."
这就是我们所拥有的。
This is what we have.
“这是我们
争取。”
"This is what we've
been fighting for."
他说一切都值得……
他是对的。
He said it was all worth it...
and he was right.